systems. The whole reason I'm bringing
up this issue of of parental control, of
deconstruction, is this whole idea of
allegiance. When you're talking to
someone and it feels like a brick wall,
that brick wall is the problem. I argue
allegiance and the building of trust is
how that wall is built. It builds a sort
of allergy to certain types of
information, certain tones. I've felt it
myself. Where does that allergy come
from? And where was it built? We have
social architects in this world building
these fantastical systems. We need to
build tools which help us focus down on
this problem. Be careful what you pledge
allegiance to.
Um because for God's sake, mayday,
mayday.